Erdem Doğanay



Jr. Web Developer

BIOGRAPHY

I worked as an intern at Digitaktek for 3 months. The company used php, jquery, javascript, html, css as programming languages. I was editing the company's websites for corporate companies. Currently, I have been working in hepapi technology for 1 year. I am making web site arrangements and development with .NET core .

PERSONAL INFO

Birth Date: 24.03.1987

Nationality: Turkey

Location: Turkey

KEY SKILLS

.NET: Expert Php: Expert HTML: Experienced CSS: Talented

.NET: 1 have been .NET

Php: 1 have been PHP

HTML: 1 have been HTML

CSS: 1 have been CSS

$C\ O\ N\ T\ A\ C\ T$

Phone: 0534474980

Mail: erdemdgny@gmail.cim

Web: www.erdem.con

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com

EXPERIENCE

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022 Digitatek, Turkey

Jr. Web Developer

I have supported many corporate web solutions of the company

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022 Hepapi Technology, United Kingdom

Jr. Web Developer

I have supported many corporate web solutions of the company

EDUCATIONS

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Ankara University, Turkey

Computer Programming

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Anadolu University, Turkey

Management Information System

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Hacettepe Üniversitesi, Bahrain

Information Technologies

LANGUAGES

English: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

Spanish: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

Turkish: C2 (Proficient)